Chris Anderson: And now we go live to Caracas
كريس أندرسون : الآن سوف نذهب إلى كراكس
to see one of Maestro Abreu's great proteges.
لكي نرى واحدة من إبداعات الميسترو أبريو
He is the new musical director of the Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra.
وهو المدير الموسيقي الجديد لأوركسترا لوس أنجليس
He's the greatest young conductor in the world.
وهو أعظم قائد أوركسترا شاب في العالم
Gustavo Dudamel!
جوستافو داداميل!
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
(Music)
(موسيقى)
Gustavo Dudamel: Hi everybody in L.A.
جوستافو داداميل: كيف حال الجميع في لو أنجليس
Hi Quincy. Hi Maestro Zander. Hi Mark.
أهلا .. جوينشي .. أهلا مايسترو زاندر .. أهلا مارك
We are very happy to have the possibility to be with you
نحن سُعداء جداً لتمكنك من الظهور معنا
in the other side of the world.
من الجانب الآخر من العالم
We can speak only with music.
يمكننا التحدث بلغة واحدة .. الموسيقى
We are very happy
ونحن سُعداء جداً
because we have the opportunity
لاننا نملك هذه الفرصة
to have this angel in the world --
التي مكنتنا من الإستماع لهذا الملاك
not only in our country, Venezuela,
ليس فقط في بلدنا .. فنزويلا
but in our world.
انما في العالم أجمع
He has given us the possibility
فلقد أعطانا القدرة
to have dreams and to make true the dreams.
على إمتلاك الأحلام وجعلها حقيقة
And here are the results
وهذه هي النتائج أمامكم
of this wonderful project
لذلك المشروع الرائع
that is The System in Venezuela.
وهذا هو النظام في فنزويلا
We hope to have, our Maestro,
ونحن نأمل يوماً أن يكون لدينا قائدنا المايسترو
to have orchestras in all the countries
وأن يكون هنالك أوركسترا في جميع دول ..
in all Americas.
الأمريكيتين
And we want to play a little piece for you
ونريد أن نعزف لكم مقطوعة صغيرة
by one of the most important composers
وهي واحدة من أهم المعزوفات لأهم مؤلفي الموسيقى
of America.
في أمريكا
A Mexican composer: Arturo Marquez.
إنه المؤلف الموسيقي المكسيكي أرتورو ماركيز
"Danzon No. 2."
معزوفة دانزون 2
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)